globalmagic.com 2004-06-06

# GLOBALMAGIC INTERNET SOLUTIONS

| 

| 

|    

**Privacy Statement**

**Overview**

GlobalMagic.com is committed to respecting the privacy of visitors to this web site. This Privacy Statement sets forth the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply to our Web site (unless a different privacy statement is specifically made applicable). By using the online forms at the GlobalMagic.com Web site, you consent to the policies and practices described in this Statement. 

Your data will be stored and processed in whole or in part in the United States. If you access the GlobalMagic.com Web site outside the United States, your usage of the site constitutes consent to the transfer of your data out of your country and to the United States. 

Our site contains links to other Web sites over which we have no control. GlobalMagic.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other Web sites to which you choose to link from a GlobalMagic.com Web site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other Web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information. This Privacy Statement applies solely to the information we collect at the GlobalMagic.com Web site, and does not apply to information we collect in any other fashion. 

**Collection and Retention of Information**  
In some areas of our Web site, GlobalMagic.com requests or may request that you provide personal information, including your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, contact information, and any other information from which your identity is discernible. In other areas, GlobalMagic.com collects or may collect demographic information that is not unique to you such as your ZIP code, age, preferences, gender, interests and favorites. Sometimes we collect or may collect a combination of the two types of information.

We also gather or may gather certain information about your use of our site, such as which areas you visit. Moreover, there is information about your computer hardware and software that is or may be collected by GlobalMagic.com. This information can include without limitation your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. 

GlobalMagic.com may sometimes afford you the opportunity to provide descriptive, cultural, behavioral, preferential and/or life style information about yourself, but it is solely up to you whether you furnish such information. If you do provide such information, you are thereby consenting to the use of that information in accordance with the policies and practices described in this Statement. For example, such information may be used for the purpose of determining your potential interest in receiving email or other communications about particular products or services. 

Please remember that if you post any of your personal information in public areas of GlobalMagic.com, such as in online forums or chat rooms, such information may be collected and used by others over whom GlobalMagic.com has no control. We are not responsible for the use made by third parties of information you post or otherwise make available in public areas of GlobalMagic.com.

**Use of Information by GlobalMagic.com**

We use the information we gather on a GlobalMagic.com Web site, whether personal, demographic, collective or technical, for the purpose of operating and improving the GlobalMagic.com Web site, fostering a positive user experience, and delivering the products and services that we offer. 

We may use your contact information in order to send you e-mail or other communications regarding updates at the GlobalMagic.com site, such as new GlobalMagic.com opportunities and additional listings which may be of interest to you. The nature and frequency of these messages will vary depending upon the information we have about you. 

We have an area where you can submit feedback. Any feedback you submit in this area becomes our property, and we can use such feedback (such as success stories) for marketing purposes or contact you for further information. 

**Disclosure of Information to Others**  
We do not disclose to third parties your personal information, combined personal and demographic information or information about your use of the GlobalMagic.com Web site (such as the areas you visit or the services you access), except as set forth in the following two subparagraphs. 

  *    We may disclose such information if legally required to do so, if requested to do so by a governmental entity or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect the rights or property of GlobalMagic.com or its affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public. 
  *    We may disclose and transfer such information to a third party who acquires all or a substantial portion of GlobalMagic Corporation's business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event GlobalMagic.com becomes the subject of a bankruptcy proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, GlobalMagic.com or its trustee in bankruptcy may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court. 

**Use of Cookies**

GlobalMagic.com uses "cookies" to help personalize and maximize your online experience and time online. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard drive by a Web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize GlobalMagic.com pages, or register for services, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information (such as user name, password and preferences). Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster and more accurate results and a more personalized site experience. When you return to the GlobalMagic.com site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customized.

You may have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline all cookies if you prefer. Alternatively, you may be able to modify your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis. If you choose to decline cookies, however, that may hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on the GlobalMagic.com Web site. 

**Security**

GlobalMagic.com has implemented reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes.

**Children**

GlobalMagic.com is not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13\. 

**Changes to Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our Privacy Statement for GlobalMagic.com, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it. If at any time, you have questions or concerns about GlobalMagic.com's Privacy Statement, please feel free to email us at [notification@GlobalMagic.com ](mailto:notification@globalmagic.com)or call us at 1-800-720-5978 and speak to one of our representatives. 

**Contact Information**

GlobalMagic.com is a name under which GlobalMagic Corporation, an Indiana corporation with its principal place of business at 5750 Castle Creek Parkway North Drive, Indianapolis, IN 46250. GlobalMagic Corporation is the legal entity which determines the purposes and means of processing the information gathered at the GlobalMagic.com Web site. 

We welcome your comments concerning this Privacy Statement. If you believe that we have not adhered to this Statement, please contact us by e-mailing us at [notification@GlobalMagic.com](mailto:notification@globalmagic.com) or by calling us at 1-800-720-5978. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem. 

Thank you for visiting GlobalMagic.com. 

|   
---|---|---|---
